{
	"questions": [
		{
			"id":1,
			"question": "Kotlin was developed by?",
			"A": "Google",
			"B": "JetBrains",
			"C": "Microsoft",
			"D": "Adobe",
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id":2,
			"question": "Which of following is used to handle null exceptions in Kotlin?",
			"A": "Elvis Operator",
			"B": "Sealed Class",
			"C": "Range",
			"D": "Lambda Expression",
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id":3,
			"question": "Which file extension is used to save Kotlin files.",
			"A": ".java",
			"B": ".kot",
			"C": ".android",
			"D": ".kt or .kts",
			"correctAnswer": 4
		},
		{
			"id":4,
			"question": "Kotlin was developed under the .......... license.",
			"A": "Apache 1.0",
			"B": "Apache 2.0",
			"C": "Apache 1.1",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id":5,
			"question": "Which of the followings constructors are available in Kotlin?",
			"A": "Primary constructor",
			"B": "Secondary constructor",
			"C": "All of the above",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 3
		},
		{
			"id":6,
			"question": "Is Kotlin compatible with the Java programming language?",
			"A": "Yes",
			"B": "No",
			"C": "All of the above",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id":7,
			"question": "What is an immutable variable?",
			"A": "A variable that cannot change, read-only",
			"B": "A variable that can be changed",
			"C": "A variable used for string interpolation",
			"D": "A variable that is null",
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id":8,
			"question": "What is correct way to create an arraylist in Kotlin?",
			"A": "val map = hashMapOf(1 to 'one', 2 to 'two', 3 to 'three')",
			"B": "enum class Color {RED, GREEN, BLUE}",
			"C": "val list = arrayListOf(1, 2, 3)",
			"D": "val set = hashSetOf(1, 2, 3)",
			"correctAnswer": 3
		},
		{
			"id":9,
			"question": "There are two types of constructors in Kotlin which are-",
			"A": "Primary & Secondary constructor",
			"B": "Default & No-arg constructor",
			"C": "Parameterized & constant Constructor",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id":10,
			"question": "Which of the following is NOT the basic data types in Kotlin?",
			"A": "Numbers",
			"B": "Strings",
			"C": "Arrays",
			"D": "Lists",
			"correctAnswer": 4
		},
		{
			"id":11,
			"question": "Can we execute Kotlin code without JVM?",
			"A": "Yes",
			"B": "No",
			"C": "May be",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id":12,
			"question": "Does Kotlin have the static keyword?",
			"A": "Yes",
			"B": "No",
			"C": "May be",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id":13,
			"question": "Is 'new' a keyword in Kotlin?",
			"A": "Yes",
			"B": "No",
			"C": "May be",
			"D": "None of the above",
			"correctAnswer": 2
		},
		{
			"id":14,
			"question": "How do you get the length of a string in Kotlin?",
			"A": "str.size",
			"B": "length(str)",
			"C": "str.lengthOf",
			"D": "isLength(str)",
			"correctAnswer": 1
		},
		{
			"id":15,
			"question": "All classes in Kotlin classes are by default?",
			"A": "public",
			"B": "final",
			"C": "sealed",
			"D": "abstract",
			"correctAnswer": 2
		}
	],
	  "quiz": {
		  "name": "kotlinQuiz"
	  }
  }
